articlepoint.org 2016-11-24

# Privacy-Policy | Article Point

Article Point Privacy Policy

* * *

ArticlePoint.org considers your privacy very seriously. It is our responsibility to protect your data which you provide to us. 

Information Collection and Use

  * ArticlePoint.org collects the personal information like your name, email address, country etc during the time of the registration.
  * We collect IP address of your system when you register or submit an article.
  * We use your personal information to communicate with you while you use our services.
  * We have rights to contact your via Email when needed.

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

  * We do not share your personal information with any third party vendors.
  * We reserve rights to share your personal information when sought by legal authorities, judicial systems etc.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

Cookies 

  * ArticlePoint.org stores logged In information in browser cookies to keep the session alive.
  * ArticlePoint.org uses third party AdServer Google Adsense to display ads on the pages that are featuring articles.
  * Google may use stored cookies to serve ads.

Change in Privacy Policy  

ArtcilePoint.org may change the privacy policy from time to time. Readers/Authors/Publishers are requested to check the policy from time to time; however, if significant changes are made, we will issue a prominent announcement on our site.
